http://www.ortofon.com/about/privacy-policy/

Share
Conducting business in a responsible and ethical manner is at the core of the Ortofon culture and has been ever since the company was established a century ago
Privacy Policy
Data controllerIn our capacity as data controller, Ortofon A/S (referred to as ”Ortofon”, ”we” or ”us”) collect your personal data when you browse our website, purchase some of our products or services and contact us via our website.
Personal data protection is a priority to us, and our focus is therefore on processing your personal data in compliance with applicable personal data protection laws.
The purpose of this privacy policy is to explain which personal data we collect when and why, how we process collected data, and to which extent data is disclosed to third par-ties. We therefore recommend that you read this privacy policy carefully.
If you have any questions in relation to this privacy policy or our processing of personal data, please contact us via support@ortofon.dk.
Data controller:Ortofon A/SStavangervej 94900 Nakskov, Denmark. Company registration number (CVR): 1701 5028
Read more about us and our company at https://www.ortofon.com/about.
Which personal data is collected and processed and for what purposes?We collect and process the following personal data and for the purposes described in this privacy policy.
User and contact informationWe collect and process the contact information you give when you purchase a product or service offered by us. We process your contact information to confirm and delivering the purchased products or services. In addition, we collect your user and contact information to be able to forward marketing material in the form of newsletters provided that you have consented to this.
RecruitmentWe collect and process the contact, educational and work related information you give when you send unsolicited application to us. We process your contact, educational and work related information for recruitment purpose provided that you have consented to this.
In addition, we use cookies to collect your information to enable your use of and access to our website via computer, tablet, phone and other devices. To learn more about our use of cookies, please read our Cookie policy.
On which legal basis do we process your personal data?We process your personal data based on your consent to our collection and processing pursuant to this privacy policy when you sign up for our newsletters or browse our website as described above. Consentbased processing of your personal data is governed by article 6(1)(a) of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
In addition, we also process your personal data when this is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party, for example when you buy one of our products or services. Processing of your personal data for performance of a contract purposes is governed by article 6(1)(b) of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
Who is your personal data disclosed to? Generally, we do not disclose your personal data and treat in confidence any personal data you have given us. We will however disclose your personal data to third party business partners (“Business Partners”) as describe in the following:
Third party transportation partnersWe collaborate with United Parcel Service (UPS) Logistics company, where we disclose your personal data to our partner should you have purchased one of our products or services in order for them to make the delivery. UPS may process your personal data solely for the purposes necessary to provide the product or service they have committed to deliver to you pursuant to their agreement with us.
Online payment service providers If you have purchased a product or service on our website, we will disclose your personal data and payment information to an online payment service provider Bambora for payment purposes. Please note that we are not responsible for a Business Partner’s or any third party’s breach of the laws governing the processing of personal data applicable from time to time. We recommend that you always read our Business Partner’s or third party’s privacy policy.
How long do we store and process your personal data?We store your personal data for a duration of 6 months, or for as long as necessary for the above purposes. Personal data that is no longer necessary for the above purposes will be deleted or anonymised.
Your influence on our processing of personal dataYou may at any time request access to the personal data we process about you, and you are entitled to receive a copy hereof.
You may at any time update or modify the user or contact information you have given us.
You may withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal data at any time. However, if you withdraw your consent, this will not affect the legality of any data processing prior to the consent withdrawal. Please note that certain personal data, such as name, email and postal address, is required for you to be part of the network and to purchase our membership packages.
Should you wish to update your contact information or to withdraw your consent to a specific processing, please contact us at support@ortofon.dk.
You may request that we transmit your personal data to you or to another data controller pursuant to applicable law.
You may object to our processing of your personal data or request that we delete any personal data, we have on you in whole or in part, or that we process your personal data only to a limited extent.
If you would like to make use of any of the above rights, or if you have any questions on our processing of your personal data, please contact us at support@ortofon.dk.
Your right to file complaint If you deem it appropriate, you are entitled to complain about our processing of your personal data. Such complaint must be submitted to the Danish Data Protection Agency (Datatilsynet). Contact information for the Danish Data Protection Agency can be found here: https://www.datatilsynet.dk/om-datatilsynet/kontakt/.
If you believe that our processing of your personal data is not legal, we urge you to contact us to discuss the matter and jointly find a satisfactory solution.
Other websitesWe may on our website link to other third party websites. Should you click on links to such websites, you will access websites that are out of our control and not comprised by this privacy policy. We recommend that you always read other websites' privacy policies.
Our right to amend this privacy policyWe reserve the right to amend this privacy policy. We will notify you of any amendment to this privacy policy subject to applicable law, and we will publish a revised version of the applicable privacy policy on our website.
We recommend that you regularly review and keep up to date with our privacy policy, including that you check for amendments hereof.
Don't have an account?
Create one for free here.
